{"data":[{"question":"Where do you eat when you're _____ the road?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"Don't get angry with me! I'm _____ your side!","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- On your side: I support\/ agree with you","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"Several participants _____ the study were unable to continue.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- In: doing or affecting a particular kind of job (in study, in education, in industry)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"The company's profits increased substantially _____ fiscal year 2002.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+  in: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ at: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ on: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"Why are you standing _____ one foot?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- On: used to say what part of someone's body is touching the ground or another surface and supporting their weight","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"There is a list of irregular verbs _____ the appendix.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- In: used to name the book, document, film etc where something or someone appears","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"I think there is a map _____ the glove compartment.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"There is someone _____ the door.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"There were more than 10,000 people _____ the concert last night.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"When did life _____ Earth begin?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"}]}